computeruser.com 2005-02-07

# ComputerUser Privacy Statement

|  |    
---|---  
  |   
  
* * *

  |  Search these directories for your best solution:Click here for ComputerTraining.

  |  Click here for your local [Internet Service Provider](http://www.cpu-net.com/)  
  | [Click for A+ Certification, Cisco Training, MCSE Certification, and MOUS exam info](http://www.trainingplanet.com/)  
  | [ Ethical Hacking Course, Information Security Training and Computer Forensics Training](http://www.infosecinstitute.com/courses/ethical_hacking_training.html)  
  | [ Click here Professional, Trade, & Vocational Colleges & Training Programs](http://www.careerschoolguide.com/)  
| A D V E R T I S E M E N T S  
---|---  
  |   
  
Please reload this page to view the headlines

|  | ComputerUser  
Privacy Policy Statement

**Frequently Asked Questions**

  * Does ComputerUser ask for personal information?
  * How Does ComputerUser use my personal information?
  * What if I make a purchase through a store affiliated with ComputerUser?
  * Will ComputerUser disclose any of my personal information?
  * Will ComputerUser use my information for direct mailings?
  * What about kids?
  * Does ComputerUser use cookies and "IP Addresses"?
  * What else should I know about my privacy?
  * For more information...

**Answers**

**Does ComputerUser ask for personal information?**

Yes, we do. ComputerUser asks for your name, e-mail address, and other personal information when you sign up for our services, such as Netquote, ISP Quick Quote, or a magazine subscription. We also ask for such information at other times, such as whenever you enter one of our contests or other promotions sponsored by ComputerUser and/or our many partners. 

* * *

**How Does ComputerUser use my personal information?**

ComputerUser goal in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with the most personalized Web experience possible and our advertisers with an efficient means to reach the right audience. By knowing a little about you, ComputerUser is able to deliver more relevant content and advertisements, and hence a better service, to you. 

* * *

**What if I make a purchase through a store affiliated with ComputerUser?**

If you place an order at an online store affiliated with ComputerUser, we will collect information from you, including your credit card and contact information. This information will be used by the merchant. ComputerUser does not own the store and all transactions and use of any customer information are the sole responsibility of the merchant. For further information regarding the merchant's use of customer information, contact that merchant store directly. 

* * *

**Will ComputerUser disclose any of my personal information?**

ComputerUser will not disclose any of your personal information, except as described below, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or to protect the rights or property of ComputerUser. 

Under confidentiality agreements, ComputerUser may match user information with third party data. Also, ComputerUser does disclose aggregated user statistics (for example, 40% of our users are female) in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. 

Additionally, if you make a purchase through a store affiliated with ComputerUser, be aware that the information that you provide, including but not limited to, your credit card number and contact information, is provided to the owner of that store. These merchants have separate privacy and data collection practices. ComputerUser has no responsiblity or liability for these independent policies.  

* * *

**Will ComputerUser use my information for direct mailings?**

Yes, but only if you give us permission. 

* * *

**What about kids?**

Naturally, the safety of children is very important to us. Kids should always ask parents for permission before sending personal information to ComputerUser, or to anyone online for that matter.

* * *

**Does ComputerUser use cookies and "IP Addresses"?**

Yes, cookies are used on CComputerUser in two ways. 

(1) We use cookies to limit voting on our polling question to one vote per person. 

(2) Our Advertising System uses cookies to try to keep you from being overwhelmed by the same ad as you traverse our site. 

_IP Addresses_

ComputerUser collects IP addresses in our log files for the purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. 

* * *

**What else should I know about my privacy?**

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through e-mail, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Furthermore, while we strive to protect your personal information, ComputerUser cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. In addition, ComputerUser partners and third party Internet sites and services accessible through ComputerUser or parties whom we inform you are collecting data in connection with sweepstakes, promotions, etc., have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of us. ComputerUser has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. The point? You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. 

* * *

**For more information... **

  * [Electronic Frontier Foundation](http://www.eff.org/) \- a civil liberties organization working to protect your rights online. 
  * [Electronic Privacy Information Center](http://epic.org/) \- established to focus public attention on emerging civil liberties issues relating to the National Information Infrastructure. 
  * [Privacy Issues Page](http://www.cdt.org/privacy/) \- from the Center for Democracy and Technology (CDT). 
  * [The EPIC Cookies Page](http://www.epic.org/privacy/internet/cookies/) \- definitions, links, and news. 
  * [How to Protect Your Privacy](http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/index.html) \- information from the Federal Trade Commission. 

|
